Jhal Hello friends, welcome to AppTalk friends, the
Q4 result date of one of the best banks of the country, ICICI Bank, has been declared
and along with that, the company has
also kept a very good gift for its shareholders, so
without wasting much time, let's
go directly to that notice, which the company has
just filed a Tejas a while ago, so
friends, we have come to that notice above,
you can see a board meeting scheduled
by the board of directors of the company on 23rd April
for the Vinash Leela Nritya, that is, the
Q4 result of ICICI Bank
is going to be announced on 23rd April, you can see it here, if
you want, you
can also read this notice by pausing the video, by the way, 23rd April is
Saturday here, so the
market will be closed on that day, but its impact will
definitely be seen on Monday when the market opens,
now see here,
a gift has been kept by the company
for its shareholders, yes, on a different
23rd, the board  The deferral will
also be discussed in the meeting. If the deferral is approved by the company's board of
directors, then
its shareholders will
get the deferral. So friends, you can say that
here we are getting a very
good update from ICICI Bank and
a sweet dish is being arranged for its shareholders by the
company.
By the way, for your information, let me
tell you that even though the market will be
closed on the 23rd, but the
entire market will wait for it, that is, wait for ICICI Bank's quarterly result because
ICICI Bank is a
leading bank in the banking sector and no doubt is a strong
company. Right now, there are two more good
companies whose Q4 result date has been declared a
few days ago. Let's take a look at them as well. So
friends, we have
come here on behalf of our other company, the
king of the sector, HDFC Bank. Yes,
friends, HDFC Bank has also
declared its result date. You
can see here that the
result of HDFC Bank and Wipro is going to come on 16th April, but
friends, let me tell you one thing, the result of 16th April is
also going to come.  It is happening on Saturday, that is why
you will get to see its pack on Monday only.
Now look at this third company here,
IT sector giant Infosys.
Yes friends, Infosys has also
declared its Q4 results date just a few days ago.
You can see here
that Infosys is going to show its results on 13th April
and at the same time, you can see here that
this time Infosys will also give dividend but
friends, you know that first the
deferral will be considered in the board meeting on 13th April.
If the deferral is approved by their board updates, only then
their shareholders will get dividend, let's
see what happens. Right now, the
result date of these three big companies has been
revealed. There are many more
good companies whose results will be
revealed gradually, but whenever it comes,
we will try to
make videos on them as soon as possible so that you can also get
updated quickly. So friends, that's all for now.
If you liked the video, then
definitely subscribe to the channel because
we talk about share market on this channel.  We keep
bringing related updates, so do
n't forget to subscribe, we will meet in the next video, till then
goodbye.